[
	{"question": "あ", "answer": "a"},
	{"question": "い", "answer": "i"},
	{"question": "う", "answer": "u"},
	{"question": "え", "answer": "e"},
	{"question": "お", "answer": "o"},
	{"question": "か", "answer": "ka"},
	{"question": "き", "answer": "ki"},
	{"question": "く", "answer": "ku"},
	{"question": "け", "answer": "ke"},
	{"question": "こ", "answer": "ko"},
	{"question": "さ", "answer": "sa"},
	{"question": "し", "answer": "shi"},
	{"question": "す", "answer": "su"},
	{"question": "せ", "answer": "se"},
	{"question": "そ", "answer": "so"},
	{"question": "た", "answer": "ta"},
	{"question": "ち", "answer": "chi"},
	{"question": "つ", "answer": "tsu"},
	{"question": "て", "answer": "te"},
	{"question": "と", "answer": "to"},
	{"question": "な", "answer": "na"},
	{"question": "に", "answer": "ni"},
	{"question": "ぬ", "answer": "nu"},
	{"question": "ね", "answer": "ne"},
	{"question": "の", "answer": "no"},
	{"question": "は", "answer": "ha"},
	{"question": "ひ", "answer": "hi"},
	{"question": "ふ", "answer": "hu"},
	{"question": "へ", "answer": "he"},
	{"question": "ほ", "answer": "ho"},
	{"question": "ま", "answer": "ma"},
	{"question": "み", "answer": "mi"},
	{"question": "む", "answer": "mu"},
	{"question": "め", "answer": "me"},
	{"question": "も", "answer": "mo"},
	{"question": "や", "answer": "ya"},
	{"question": "ゆ", "answer": "yu"},
	{"question": "よ", "answer": "yo"},
	{"question": "ら", "answer": "ra"},
	{"question": "り", "answer": "ri"},
	{"question": "る", "answer": "ru"},
	{"question": "れ", "answer": "re"},
	{"question": "ろ", "answer": "ro"},
	{"question": "わ", "answer": "wa"},
	{"question": "を", "answer": "wo"},
	{"question": "ん", "answer": "n"},
]